Onyeka Ezeh

Link to my portfolio site - https://heuristic-jackson-57b077.netlify.app/#home

Yaba

officialcodesofowen@gmail.com

+234 907 580 2843

Hi, my name is Owen and I am a Front End Developer and WordPress Web Developer from Lagos, Nigeria with over 3 years of experience designing, building and customizing websites, specifically in Front End Development. How can I help? I have a passion for building responsive, engaging sites that focus on user experience, content and design. You need a site that converts? SEO driven? Responsive and user friendly? An experienced developer who would take your project and treat it with utmost priority? Again, while there may be a lot who can provide these services, I seek to provide them with a comprehensive, pre-determined strategy to assure your return on investment. Why hire me? I am a certified Web Developer and I take on projects that I know are well within my line of expertise. I have strong knowledge of the languages needed and required to deign and build responsive sites, e.g HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Jquery, PHP. So what are we waiting for? Let' get started! Also, do not hesitate to reach out with any questions you have. I look forward to working with you

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Personal Details

Currently Employed: No **Date of Birth:** 2002-03-31

Highest Level of Education: National Diploma

Industry: Software Development **NYSC Status:** Not Applicable

Work Experience

Frontend developer

Revamped Skincare - Lagos January 2022 to Present

Web developer

Rhixe Company - Lagos July 2021 to January 2022

Designed and developed the official site for Rhixe Company. A web development & IT services company

Mobile App Developer Intern

Bincom ICT Solutions - Lagos August 2020 to February 2021

Education

National Diploma in Urban and regional planning

Yabatech - Yaba

February 2019 to August 2021

Certificate in Frontend Development

Coursera - UC Davis - Lagos October 2020 to February 2021

Certificate in Web development

Coursera - UC Davis - Lagos March 2020 to August 2020

Skills

- microsoft office (2003-current) (6 years)
- Html, CSS3, Javascript and python. (3 years)
- Project management. (1 year)
- Bootstrap 5, Sass and React. (1 year)
- WordPress (3 years)
- Data entry (5 years)

Certifications and Licenses

Web development

March 2020 to Present

Publications

Xamehi Tv

http://Xamehi.tv

November 2021

A movie streaming site like netflix.

Rhixescans

http://rhixescans.com

October 2021

A manga reading site

Owen's Portfolio

https://heuristic-jackson-57b077.netlify.app/#home

February 2022

My personal portfolio site

Fast Food Prototype https://pedantic-goldwasser-008aef.netlify.app/#

September 2021

Developed the user interface for a fast food ordering site